adzmedia.com 2014-06-25

# AdzMedia.Com | Global Mobile Ad Network | Mobile AdNetwork | Mobile Advertising | Mobile Advertising and Publishing Platform | Apps Advertising and Publishing Platform | InApp Ads | Apps Ads | Mobile Ads | CPC Ads | CPI Ads | CPM Ads | CPA Ads | CPL Ads | CPS Ads | Geo Location Based Advertising | Operator Based Advertising | Tablet Advertising

### Privacy

## Collection of Data

We collect personally identifiable information (PII) when voluntarily submitted by our visitors. This information is used to fulfill specific requests and services. 

The Site may use cookie and tracking technology depending on the features offered. Cookie and tracking technology are useful for gathering information such as browser type and operating system, tracking the number of visitors to the Site, and understanding how visitors use the Site. Cookies can also help customize the Site for visitors. Personal information cannot be collected via cookies and other tracking technology, however, if you previously provided personally identifiable information, cookies may be tied to such information. Aggregate cookie and tracking information may be shared with third parties.

## Distribution of Information

We may share information with governmental agencies or other companies assisting us in fraud prevention or investigation.

We may do so when: 

(1) permitted or required by law or, (2) trying to protect against or prevent actual or potential fraud or unauthorized transactions or, (3) investigating fraud which has already taken place. The information is not provided to these companies for marketing purposes.

## Commitment to Data Security

Your personally identifiable information is kept secure. Only authorized employees, agents and contractors (who have agreed to keep information secure and confidential) have access to this information.

## Other web sites

Our web site may contain links to other web sites which are outside our control and are not covered by this Privacy Policy. If you access other sites using the links provided, the operators of these sites may collect information from you which will be used by them in accordance with their privacy policy, which may differ from ours.

## Internet-based transfers

Given that the Internet is a global environment, using the Internet to collect and process personal data necessarily involves the transmission of data on an international basis. Therefore, by browsing this web site and communicating electronically with us, you acknowledge and agree to our processing of personal data in this way.
